# PAWEŁ SĘKARA

# DETAILS

Kraków Poland +48 515 449 866 pawel.sekara@gmail.com

# - LINKS -

Linkedin (/in/pawelsekara)

# LANGUAGES

Polish English

# SKILLS

Java

Kotlin

Spring

SQL

Microservices

**AWS** 

Maven

Git

Docker

Linux

# HOBBIES

Baking, Welding, 3D Printing, Shooting sports

# PROFILE

Passionate software engineer with 10 years of commercial experience in various technologies. Experienced with the latest development tools and frameworks. Able to self-manage in independent projects, as well as collaborate as part of a team. Always willing to learn new things and share it with others.

Started programming at the age of 8 using Commodore 64 and never regretted that.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

# Java & Kotlin Backend Developer at Codewise

July 2018 — Present

Development and maintenance of Voluum marketing platform.

- Microservices development using Spring Boot/Security/Data/MVC in Java & Kotlin
- Improving stability and availability of business critical part of the system
- · Created secured infrastructure on AWS using Terraform
- Writing integration & unit tests
- · Conducting code reviews & mentoring

Java, Kotlin, Spring, AWS, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, Redis, Cassandra, Docker, Maven, Nginx, Jenkins, Datadog

# Senior iOS Developer at Codewise

July 2015 — March 2019

- Development of native Voluum and ZeroPark applications in Swift.
- Creating SDKs in Objective-C.

# iOS Developer at ZineINC

December 2013 — June 2015

• Development and deployment of native ZineINC application for iOS.

# Mobile Developer & Team Lead at Codete

July 2012 — December 2013

- Development of various native iOS and Android applications.
- Leading mobile developers team.

# EDUCATION

Master's Degree Computer Science, Uniwersytet Jagielloński w Krakowie January 2013 — December 2016

Bachelor's Degree Computer Science, Uniwersytet Jagielloński w Krakowie January 2010 — December 2013

# COURSES

AWS Architect - Intermediate

Communication is your work, Leaders Island

Mobile applications security